liquidspace.com 2019-03-16

# LiquidSpace

## **Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy has been updated; Summary of the changes can be found at the bottom of the Policy.

This privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) describes how LiquidSpace, Inc (LiquidSpace) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site liquidspace.com and Mobile Software. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. By using, accessing or participating in the Service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings set forth in the Terms of Use (located at liquidspace.com/Home/Terms-Of-Use).

If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@liquidspace.com. 

LiquidSpace complies with the U.S.–E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S.–Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. LiquidSpace has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view LiquidSpace’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. If we do this, we will post a notice that we have made material changes to this Privacy Policy on the Site for at least 7 days before the changes are posted and will indicate at the bottom of the Privacy Policy the date this policy was last revised. Any revisions to this Privacy Policy will become effective (i) on the effective date or (ii) the first time you access or use the Service after any such changes. If you do not agree to abide by this or any future Privacy Policy, do not use, access or participate in (or continue to use, access or participate in) the Service. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**The Information We Collect**

We collect and store information to provide you a better overall experience and present you with the most relevant products and ads possible. When you use the Service you provide us with three types of information: (i) information you submit via the Service, (ii) information regarding your use of the Service collected by us as you interact with the Service and (iii) information from other sources.

  * Information you submit via the Service 

  * Through the registration process you may provide us with your name, company affiliation, email address, telephone number, physical address, and other information that may be requested during the registration process on the Site.

  * If you wish to create an account that requires payment of a fee, or use services offered via the Site that require payment of a fee, a valid credit card number or other payment information may be required. By submitting your payment information, you authorize LiquidSpace to access and use this information in order to provide you with and accept payment for the Service.

  * When you use the Service you may submit information and content to your Profile, send messages, perform searches, submit reviews, and otherwise transmit information to other Users. We store this information and registration information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features.

  * Information we get from your use of the Service

  * When you enter the Site, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all LiquidSpace visitors.

  * When you download and use our Mobile Software, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID").

  * We store certain information from your browser using “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. We also use persistent cookies to remember sign-in status, coupon availability, search preferences, and Space origination information so that you do not have to enter it again the next time you visit.

  * You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Site.

  * We are a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) and adhere to the NAI Code of Conduct.You can opt-out of receiving targeted advertising based on data collected via your browser by using the NAI’s opt-out tool, which can be found [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) .  When you opt out, we will stop (a) collecting information about your interests via your browser and (b) serving you targeted advertisements based on the data collected via your browser.

  * Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content, advertising and marketing on our site as well as off our site

  * While you may disable the usage of cookies through your browser settings, we do not respond to a “Do Not Track”  signal in the HTTP header from your browser or mobile application. We may use analytics to track responses from third-party ads such as search engines and social networks.

  * We use analytics tools like Google Analytics and Pingdom to track application usage, performance, and availability as well as your response to LiquidSpace content, ads and placements, including on search engines and social networks.For more information on how Google uses data when you use our site or app, please visit .

  * We may, either directly or through Third Parties we partner with, track your interaction with the Service and ads on the site and off the site for the purposes of LiquidSpace customer support, analytics, research, product development, fraud prevention, risk assessment, regulatory compliance and investigation.

  * The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

  * If you use the Mobile Software, your location may be tracked on the mobile device on which the Mobile Software is installed. LiquidSpace will not collect, transmit or otherwise use this information without your permission. We use location data to provide you relevant search results for spaces in your area. As a Guest, you can control when Hosts or other Guests can see your location through your privacy settings. To opt out of location tracking, please change your settings at the device level.

  * Information from other sources

  * If you sign up for LiquidSpace using your social media account, link your LiquidSpace account to your social media account, or use other LiquidSpace social media features, we may access information about you via that social media provider in accordance with the provider’s policies.

We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

**Minors**

LiquidSpace does not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for LiquidSpace or send any information about you to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 18 may provide any information to or on LiquidSpace. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a minor under 18, please contact us at privacy@liquidspace.com.

**Use of Information Obtained by LiquidSpace**

We use the information we collect from our services to enable your access to our products, enhance our products, protect the site and our customers, and to offer tailored content, like more relevant search results and ads.

Once you register with LiquidSpace, you may create your Profile. Your Profile and contact information are displayed to other Users, including Hosts at at spaces at which you make or request reservations and tours.

We may also send you service-related announcements and marketing communications on the site, across other websites, and through email. Examples include promotions, new product/service messages, ads for the service and partner offers. Generally, you may opt out of such emails by following the unsubscribe option included in each email; however, LiquidSpace reserves the right to send you account-related notices such as reservation confirmation emails even if you opt out of all marketing-related emails.

LiquidSpace provides push notifications for upcoming reservations. To turn off push notifications, please edit your personal settings on your device.

Profile information and your reservation activity is used by LiquidSpace primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the Service and to be presented to other Users. The amount of such information presented to other Users will depend on your relationship with those Users (e.g., whether they are following you, or you are following them, as permitted by the Service, or whether you were referred to the Service by them).

If you register for the Service via a referral from a Professional, LiquidSpace will inform the Professional when you register for the Service and begin browsing listings on the Service, and will provide the Professional with information regarding reservations that you book. In some cases, other Users may be able to supplement your Profile or contribute information about your Space (if you are a Host), including by submitting comments and reviews. You consent to LiquidSpace making such information available to other Users and the public.

You may change the privacy settings of your profile through your account portal. Information from your Profile may be available to our third party service provider for search engines. This is primarily so that potential users may be able to find you.

LiquidSpace may use non-identifiable aggregate data (based partly on IP addresses) collected through the Service to analyze Service usage and system performance. Such data may be used by LiquidSpace and shared with third parties in any manner.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**

You may choose to provide information about you, your company or organization or, if you are a Host, your Space to other Users and to the public by providing such information on public areas of the Site (“Public Information”). Public Information consists of information that is posted by you on areas of the Site accessible by other Users and/or the public, such as Space descriptions. Public information does not include information you submit to us but do not post on areas of the Site accessible by other Users and/or the public, such as billing and payment information (“Non-Public Information”).

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We share your Non-Public Information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is reasonably necessary to offer the Service, legally required or permitted by you. For example:

  * We may provide Non-Public Information to service providers who help us bring you the services we offer, such as hosting the service at a co-location facility, sending email updates about LiquidSpace, removing repetitive information from our User lists, processing payments, or to provide search results or links. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your Non-Public Information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any of your Non-Public Information, we implement reasonable contractual protections limiting the use of that Non-Public Information to the provision of services to LiquidSpace.

  * We may be required to disclose Non-Public Information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. Additionally, we may share Non-Public Information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Service or using the LiquidSpace name, or to prevent imminent harm. This may include sharing Non-Public Information with other companies, lawyers, agents, government agencies or to any third party with your prior consent to do so.

  * We may offer to provide services jointly with other companies on the Service, and we may share Non-Public Information with that company in connection with such offer or your use of that service.

  * If the ownership of all or substantially all of the LiquidSpace business, or individual business units or assets owned by LiquidSpace that are related to the Site, were to change, your Non-Public Information may be transferred to the new owner. In any such transfer of information, your Non-Public Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

  * If we have a separate agreement with a company we believe to be your employer or company for whom we believe you work as a contractor (as determined in each case by your email domain), we may provide your User ID, email address and reservation activity to that company so that you may be included within an arrangement that we have with such company. We will notify you if we provide this information to a company and you may elect not to participate in any such arrangement by contacting us at support@liquidspace.com and stating that you do not wish to participate in such arrangement.

  * When you use the Service, certain information you post or share with third parties (including other Users), such as comments, reviews or other information, may be shared with other Users in accordance with the privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose confidential information in your Profile or when posting comments, reviews or other submissions, this information may become publicly available.

  * Your posting of Public Information to public areas of the Site constitutes your consent to share such Public Information publicly. Please be aware that Public Information will be accessible by both Users and the general public. Nothing in this Privacy Policy shall restrict LiquidSpace’s right to use Public Information. To request removal of your personal information from public areas of the Site, please contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

  * We use Plaid Technologies, Inc. (“Plaid”) to gather user data from financial institutions. By using our service, you grant us and Plaid the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution. You agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the [Plaid Privacy Policy](https://plaid.com/legal) .

**Links**

LiquidSpace may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage Users to be aware when they leave the Site to read the privacy statements of other web sites that collect personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by LiquidSpace via the Site.

**Single Sign-on**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Linked In Open ID provider give you the option to post information about your activities on this web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Third Party Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on LiquidSpace are sometimes delivered (or “served”) directly to Users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 gifs”) to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. LiquidSpace does not have access to or control of the cookies or other technologies that may be used by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on LiquidSpace unless you choose to share it with them. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by contacting us at support@liquidspace.com. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by LiquidSpace and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

**Changing or Removing Information**

Users may modify or delete their Profile information by logging into their account. Removed information may persist in backup copies but will not be generally available to other Users. Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other Users (e.g., sending a message to another User) you generally cannot remove such communications from the Site.

Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

**Security**

LiquidSpace takes reasonable precautions to protect Users’ Non-Public Information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number on our order forms or transmit location data, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore we cannot guarantee absolute security. If you have any questions about security please contact us.

**Data Transfer**

The data protection laws in the United States differ from those applicable in other countries, including the country in which you reside. By providing LiquidSpace with your personal information, you consent to the collection, transfer and processing of your personal information to and from the United States and agree that your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts or law enforcement in the United States according to the laws of the United States.

**Contacting LiquidSpace**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or LiquidSpace’s privacy practices in general, please contact us as provided for below. You may also contact us to require that we provide you with a copy of your Non-Public Information within our control, to have us correct any erroneous information, to discontinue receipt of certain types of communications or to ask us to delete any of your Non-Public Information we have stored that is no longer required for the purpose for which it was collected. We will respond to your request to access Non-Public Information within 30 days.

Nanci Anderson

2225 E. Bayshore Road, Suite 200

Palo Alto, CA 94303

Phone : 855-254-7843

Email : privacy@liquidspace.com

Last revised on May 1, 2016

Summary of Changes to LiquidSpace Privacy Policy

This summary is intended to facilitate your review and understanding of the changes to the Privacy Policy. However, please take the time to read the full document, as you will be bound by its terms when you view, access or otherwise use LiquidSpace’s online services.

_Some highlights to the revisions to the Privacy Policy follow:_

We have updated the Privacy Policy to clarify the type of information we collect and expand on how we use some of the information for marketing and advertising.

We also generally updated the format to make it easier to read.

 http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/

 This “Do Not Track” statement is intended to replace the original DNT statement deleted below
